

PROFILE

A Geologist and Biostratigrapher with experience in in well logging and well analysis using microfossils to determine relative age and environment of deposition of strata.

A Front-End Developer with years of hands-on experience designing.

hands-on experience designing, developing, and implementing web applications. I develop responsive and performant web applications with variety of development languages and modern technologies. I seek opportunities for further development, focused on excellence, leadership, values individual vision and a sense of teamwork.

CONTACT

PHONE: +2348168274810

EMAIL: adeniyiadedayo95@gmail.com

ADENIYI ADEDAYO

EDUCATION

| Obafemi Awolowo University, lle-Ife BSc Geology | 2013 - 2019 |
|---|-------------|
| Roseful International High School, Osogbo. West African Examination Council. (SSCE) | 2007 - 2009 |
| Bisola College of Art & Science, Osogbo. West African Examination Council. (O Level) | 2009 - 2012 |

PERSONAL QUALITIES AND SKILLS

- Computer Skill: Microsoft Office Tool at Intermediate Level.
- Front-end Developer: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Vue.js
- Effective communication and problem solving skills
- Good team spirit
- High level of honesty and integrity
- Ability to work with little or no supervision

WORK EXPERIENCE

TRANSERVE DISC TECHNOLOGIES LIMITED SEPTEMBER 2020 - FEBRUARY 2021.

SOFT SKILLS

Effective communication skills

Proficiency in software development

Project management skills

Great team spirit and work ethic

Adaptability

INTERESTS

- Reading.
- Article Write-ups
- Computer Programming
- Traveling

REFERENCES

- ★ Mr Fredrick Odogbo Ikeja Electric 08098353809
- ★ Mr. Obunike Okonkwo
 Transerve Disc Technologies Limited
 08150616671 07085128510

Administrative officer where my tasks include but not limited to:

- ★ Office Maintenance.
- ★ Book keeping.
- ★ Vehicles Maintenance.

WORK EXPERIENCE

HNG17

APRIL 2020 - AUGUST 2020

- ★ I developed user interfaces with modern JavaScript frameworks, HTML5 and CSS3.
- ★ I collaborated with product managers, testers, and developers to initiate process improvements.
- ★ I collaborated with a product designer to create a unique startup.